(Alfred:)Leonard, if you don't mind,
I-I think I'm a little tired.
(Alfred:)I'm gonna call it a night.
(Leonard:)Sure, Dad.
(Alfred:)I'm a little
tuckered out myself,
(Mary:)so I will see you all
in the morning.
(Alfred:)Would you like
to share a cab?
(Mary:)That would be fine.
(Alfred:)Where are you staying?
I'm at the Westin.
(Alfred:)Oh, so am I.
(Alfred:)Can I interest you
in a nightcap?
(Mary:)I think that you could.
(Leonard:)What is happening there?
(Sheldon:)I think it's pretty obvious.
(Sheldon:)They don't want dessert
'cause they filled up on bread.
(Sheldon:)She's still not answering.
(Leonard:)My father's not texting me back.
(singsongy): 'Cause they both
turned their phones off.
(Sheldon:)I don't like this at all.
(Leonard:)I don't like it either.
(Mary:)Really?
(laughing):
'Cause I love it.